<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../helpproject.xsl" ?>
<topic template="Default" lasteditedby="rbwinst-pr" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../helpproject.xsd">
  <title translate="true">Abstract</title>
  <body>
    <header>
      <para styleclass="Heading1"><text styleclass="Heading1" translate="true">Abstract</text></para>
    </header>
    <para styleclass="Heading2_atoc_"><text styleclass="Heading2_atoc_" translate="true">Version 2:</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true">ModelMuse is a graphical user interface (GUI) for MODFLOW-2005 and PHAST. &#160;This software package provides a GUI for creating the flow and transport input file for PHAST and the input files for MODFLOW-2005. &#160;In ModelMuse, the spatial data for the model are independent of the grid, and the temporal data are independent of the stress periods. &#160;Being able to input these data independently allows the user to redefine the spatial and temporal discretization at will. &#160;This report describes the basic concepts required to work with ModelMuse. &#160;These basic concepts include the model grid, data sets, formulas, objects, the method used to assign values to data sets, and model features.</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true">The ModelMuse main window has a top, front, and side view of the model that can be used for editing the model, and a 3-D view of the model that can be used to display properties of the model. &#160;ModelMuse has tools to generate and edit the model grid. It also has a variety of interpolation methods and geographic functions that can be used to help define the spatial variability of the model. &#160;ModelMuse can be used to execute both MODFLOW-2005 and PHAST and can also display the results of MODFLOW-2005 models. An example of using ModelMuse with MODFLOW-2005 is included in this report. Several additional examples are described in the help system for ModelMuse, which can be accessed from the Help menu.</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Heading2_atoc_"><text styleclass="Heading2_atoc_" translate="true">Version 3:</text></para>
    <para styleclass="Normal"><text styleclass="Normal" translate="true">This report 1) describes modifications to ModelMuse, as described in U.S. Geological Survey (USGS) Techniques and Methods (TM) 6–A29 (Winston, 2009), to add support for the Saturated-Unsaturated Transport model (SUTRA) (Voss and Provost, 2002; version of September 22, 2010) and 2) supplements USGS TM 6–A29. Modifications include changes to the main ModelMuse window where the model is designed, addition of methods for generating a finite-element mesh suitable for SUTRA, defining how some functions should apply when using a finite-element mesh rather than a finite-difference grid (as originally programmed in ModelMuse), and applying spatial interpolation to angles. In addition, the report describes ways of handling objects on the front view of the model and displaying data. A tabulation contains a summary of the new or modified dialog boxes.</text></para>
  </body>
</topic>
